# **Andre Burke**

## **Summary of Qualifications**

Over 4 years of professional information technology experience. Significant experience in .NET, C#, Entity Framework, MVC, Web API, and more. Solid developer with excellent problem-solving and communication skills. Passionate about data, logic, and technology. I'm always willing to embrace new challenges and learn new technologies.

#### **Technical Skills**

Technologies/Tools: C#, .NET Framework/Core, Entity Framework/Core, Git, MVC,

Web API, Restful Web Services, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Software Patterns, SOA, OOP, ETL. Experience with application

deployment on IIS and Nginx

Computer Systems: Windows, Mac OS

DB Technologies: Microsoft SQL Server

### **Professional Experience**

Software Engineer, SelectQuote Insurance Services

March 2021 – Present

- C#, .NET Core, MVC, Web API, EntityFrameworkCore, T-SQL, AWS
  - Team lead on the SelectRecruit squad. SelectRecruit or SLRC was the internal recruiting software used at SelectQuote.
  - Integrated Paperform into the SelectRecruit CRM.
  - Eliminated blocking asynchronous calls which would cause stalls in the recruiting agents' workflow while using the CRM.
  - Spent time refactoring legacy code to follow more up-to-date .NET Core development practices while utilizing 3rd party libraries such as MediatR and AutoMapper.

**Software Developer**, Integrated Distribution Services *C#, .NET, ASP.NET, MVC, Web API, EF, SQL* 

April 2019 – March 2021

- Overall responsibilities involve moving large volumes of order data from customer storefronts/platforms like Shopify, NetSuite, etc. to warehousing software.
- Vastly improved querying speed of shipment confirmation data.
- Built a batch picking tool to batch pick warehouse items which saved hours of manual labor.
- Built out data visualization and reporting dashboards pulled data together from multiple sources with ETL jobs.

### **Software Engineer**, Supplemental Health Care

February 2018 – April 2019

C#, .NET Core, ASP.NET, Web API, MVC, IoC, EF, SQL

- Using new and old Microsoft technologies to expand the features in our medical staffing application.
- Agile and Scrum methodologies.
- Creating software to assist recruiters with the hiring funnel.
- Designed a new ASP .NET Core Web API project, file infrastructure feature, and ASP.NET Core MVC Microsites project.
- Introduced an IoC container and Dependency Injection into the main TRM application.

### **Software Developer**, hh2 Cloud Services

October 2016 – January 2018

C#, ASP.NET, Web API, SOAP, NHibernate, SQL

- Worked solely on backend technology with C#, .NET Framework, and SQL.
- Built, maintained, and enhanced cloud construction software.
- Worked with NHibernate for data layer access.
- Created a file infrastructure feature, email notification feature, and an entity auditor feature.

# **Project Experience**

#### Paperform Integration

ASP.NET Core, MVC, Entity Framework Core

- Captured form data from Paperform and displayed it in the SelectRecruit CRM.
- Configured webhooks to capture the completed forms.
- Built a new table structure and an improved v2 structure and migrated the data from v1 to v2 via SQL.

#### **Batch Picking Tool**

ASP.NET, MVC, Entity Framework

- Interfaced internal source code with the WMS software.
- Easily allowed staff to batch pick large waves of items.
- The tool saved our operations team hours of time from their processes every day.

#### Job API

ASP.NET Core, Web API, Entity Framework Core

- Created to abstract access to SHC's data layers from external clients.
- Utilizes Microsoft's built-in DI service collection with the repository pattern.
- Added a file upload/download piece for managing documents such as resumes.

#### **Education and Training**

Associate of Science, Computer Science

University of Utah

Certifications and Training:

• Web Development Certificate – V School